ALLISON PITTMAN

pittman.ally@gmail.com | https://avyrie.github.io/SocialMediaPortfolio/

Summary

Hard-working and highly adaptable Social Media Manager and Software Engineer with experience in multiple fields including 5+ years of management in a small business environment and 10+ years in customer service/support. I am a problem solver who is passionate about finding new and exciting ways to connect with and satisfy my clients. As a customer-oriented professional, I excel at analyzing and resolving issues while displaying compassion and empathy and pride myself on being very teachable and adaptive to each new role I undertake in my professional career.

Skills

Social media management, marketing, data entry, research, Microsoft Office, scheduling, sales, administrative assistance, professional writing, web design (HTML, CSS, JS, Node.js, Express.js, React.js, Git, WordPress, Git, VSCode, MongoDB), Canva, promotional content creation, customer service, client resolution, new employee training.

Education

- **BS Biology** | George Mason University
- Software Engineering Immersive Program Completion
 Certification | General Assembly

Experience

ManyBuild

Software Engineer (Contract) | Feb 2021 - present

• Complete and integrate various projects ranging in difficulty across multiple repositories within the ManyBuild complex using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, Firebase, and React.js.

Bark 'N Bubbles

Social Manager | 2016 - present

- Handle client inquiries made through social media accounts
- Update social media content on Instagram, Twitter, and Facebook to reflect positive and informational situations

Luke & Co Fine Pet Supply & Outfitter

Inventory Specialist | Oct 2019 - May 2020

- Populated and confirmed large weekly orders using Lightspeed that routinely exceeded \$10,000 through major vendors and direct-to-order companies.
- Maintained accurate inventory levels for over 15,000 SKU's using virtual spreadsheets and physical stock checks.
- Created relationships with various company reps and oversaw acquisition of new inventory.
- Assisted clients with information and suggestions based on unique needs about the company's products and services.

Metro Offices

Area Center Coordinator | Feb 2019 - Sep 2019

- Assisted clients with a myriad of questions and requests including equipment loans, meeting room booking, center tours, service quotes, and more.
- Maintained open communication with other centers within the company to ensure clients were taken care of regardless of location.
- Screened/directed incoming phone calls in a manner specific to each company receiving answering service with a pleasant demeanor and accurate transfers.
- Organized and hosted several events at several centers celebrating various holidays and appreciation days.

^{*}Additional Experience is available upon request